[
  {
    "questionText": "Who is Beach Bunny Discord's second favorite artist?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ed Sheeran"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who was the lawyer in the Beach Bunny Discord cease and desist?",
    "correctAnswer": "Saul Goodman"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What is Beach Bunny's #1 streamed song on Spotify?",
    "correctAnswer": "Prom Queen"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Is Beach Bunny a band or a single person?",
    "correctAnswer": "Band. Person? It's not clear."
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Is Beach Bunny a TikTok band?",
    "correctAnswer": "Yes. (no?) It's complicated."
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who is Jon?",
    "correctAnswer": "Beach Bunny's drummer."
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which two Discord bots were at war in the Beach Bunny Discord server?",
    "correctAnswer": "Chuu and .fmbot"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What song did the Beach Bunny Discord community produce a cover of?",
    "correctAnswer": "Oxygen"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What Beach Bunny Discord community event did we do once and never again?",
    "correctAnswer": "Karaoke"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who in the Beach Bunny Discord has the most messages according to MEE6 bot?",
    "correctAnswer": "saltlord"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who founded the Beach Bunny Discord server?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ian"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "When is the Beach Bunny Discord server's birthday?",
    "correctAnswer": "November 7"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who is Ekiya?",
    "correctAnswer": "Good Owner Boi"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which city is Beach Bunny from?",
    "correctAnswer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What is the title of Beach Bunny's debut full-length album, released in 2020?",
    "correctAnswer": "Honeymoon"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who was the artist for the Honeymoon album cover?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lili"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who makes all the official Beach Bunny Discord server Bots?",
    "correctAnswer": "NoahH99"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What famous actor was featured in the music video for Karaoke?",
    "correctAnswer": "Bob Odenkirk"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Name the Beach Bunny Discord Moderators.",
    "correctAnswer": "Emma, NatB, seanbagel"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Where was the Beach Bunny Discord first announced?",
    "correctAnswer": "r/beachbunny"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Who is opening for Beach Bunny on the Tunnel Vision USA tour?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pool Kids, Jayla Kai, Scarlet Demore"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What bot in the Beach Bunny Discord is permanently offline?",
    "correctAnswer": "(Good Bots) Don't Get Used"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What is the name of Beach Bunny's music festival?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pool Party"
  }
]
